<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>

<schemalist>
  <schema path='/com/canonical/indicator/appmenu/hud/search/'
          id='com.canonical.indicator.appmenu.hud.search'
          gettext-domain='indicator-appmenu'>
    <key type='u' name='indicator-penalty'>
      <default>50</default>
      <summary>The penalty given to a menu item being in an indicator</summary>
      <description>
        In order to have the application's menu items appear higher in the search results a slight penalty is
        given to the indicator menu items. This value represents the percentage of that penalty so a value of
        '50' is a 50% additional to the calculated distance.
      </description>
    </key>

    <key type='u' name='add-penalty'>
      <default>100</default>
      <summary>Penalty for extra characters added to the search</summary>
      <description>
        The penalty for each extra character in the search string that does not appear in the text of a menu
        item.

        This penalty would be applied if the user typed "fiile" when searching against the menu item "File", for
        example.
      </description>
    </key>

    <key type='u' name='drop-penalty'>
      <default>100</default>
      <summary>Penalty applied if a character is dropped</summary>
      <description>
        The penalty for each character dropped from the search string, as compared with the text of a menu item.
        This only applies to missing characters that are not at the end of the search term.

        This penalty would be applied if the user typed "fle" when searching against the menu item "File", for
        example.
      </description>
    </key>

    <key type='u' name='end-drop-penalty'>
      <default>20</default>
      <summary>Penalty applied if a character is dropped from the end</summary>
      <description>
        The penalty for each missing character at the end of a search term.

        This penalty would be applied if the user typed "fil" when searching against the menu item "File", for
        example.
      </description>
    </key>

    <key type='u' name='swap-penalty'>
      <default>150</default>
      <summary>Penalty applied when the characters are not the same</summary>
      <description>
        The penalty for each substituted character in the search term.

        The penalty would be applied if the user typed "fike" when searching against the menu item "File", for
        example.
      </description>
    </key>

    <key type='u' name='max-distance'>
      <default>30</default>
      <summary>The highest distance value that is shown in the results</summary>
      <description>
        After the distances are calculated (including the indicator penalty) then all values above this max are
        dropped. This means that the history for those entries aren't looked up as well.
      </description>
    </key>
  </schema>
</schemalist>
